以下是一个被删减的片段
The following scenes were deleted
原来是在"第八季第三集 告知罗斯"这集
from the episode "THE ONE WHERE RACHEL TELLS ROSS"
现在在这里是第一次向大家呈现
and are being presented here for the first time
故事的概要是，钱德跟机场的安保人员开玩笑
The story involved Chandler joking with security at an airport
这集即将要在2001年911事件的2个礼拜之后向公众播映
and was to air two weeks after the events of Sep.11, 2001
根据这个原因，我们决定替换原始的故事
In light of this, we decided to replace the original story
作为本出戏的历史一部分组成
As part of the history of the show,
我们希望大家能看到这个被删除的画面
we hope that the scenes can now be viewed
好让大家了解这出戏原本的意思
in the spirit which they were originally intended
搭计程车没问题，又不塞车，按照我的计划来都行得通嘛
No problem getting a cab, no traffic. My way totally works
是呀，我感觉轻松自如
Ya, I feel totally relaxed, totally calm.
快去！快去！
Go, go, go, go, go!
让我看看哦…你们要飞住拿骚(巴哈马首都)
Let's see, you're on the flight to Nassau.
宾先生，你坐25J号座位，宾太太，你坐25K号座位
Mr. Bing, you'll be in 25J. And Mrs. Bing, you'll be in 25K.
呵呵，宾太太…
Hmm, Mrs. Bing
这个称呼的确有趣
It is a funny name.
她没在笑这个名字
She's not laughing at the name.
我们刚结婚，现在在度蜜月
We just got married. We're going on our honeymoon.
哦，真的？恭喜呀
Oh Really? Congratulations.
让我看看我还能为你们做些什么
You know what, let me see what I can do.
有个取消机票的申请，我可以把你们换进头等舱
There was a cancelation, I can bump you into first class.
哇，谢谢
Whoa, Thank you.
看，若我们到早一点儿的话，头等舱的座位就可能没了
See? If We got here earlier, those seats might not have been available
和解生效
Compromise works.
我的名字都叫“宾太太”了，我还和解得不够吗？
My name is "Mrs. Bing". Haven't I compromised enough
你能快点吗？
Could you hurry up?
嘿，我以前从没出过问题，现在也不会
Hey, I have never set one of these off before, and I'm not about to start now.
哦对了，等一下
Oh, wait a second
我的脚链，这是贴身的哦
My anklet. That was a close one.
哦也
Yes!
嘿嘿，看那儿，联邦法律
Hey Hey, look at that Federal law
严禁任何关于劫机或炸弹爆炸的笑话
prohibits any joking regarding aircraft highjacking or bombing
放心，你们不用担心我
You don't have to worry about me, man.
我会非常严肃地携带我的炸弹的
I'll take my bombs very seriously.
先生，请跟我们来一趟
Sir, you wanna come with us?
不！慢着，钱德！
No, wait, Chandler, wait!
这不算数！倒着走不算！
That doesn't count. Backwards doesn't count!
真搞笑，我只不过是说了个笑话
Look, this is ridiculous. I was just making a joke.
我是说我知道标语写着“不准开炸弹玩笑”
I mean I know the sign says, "No jokes about bombs"
难道标语不应该写“严禁炸弹”吗？
but shouldn't the sign really say,"No bombs"?
我的意思是说，我们真正应该担心的
I mean isn't that the guy we really have to worry about here
应该是带着炸弹的，而不是开“炸弹玩笑”的人
the guy with the bombs, not the guy who jokes about his bombs
我没有炸弹啊 若我有的话，我压根不会开这玩笑
not that I have bombs, because if I did, I probably wouldn't joke about it.
我会非常低调不让别人知道的呀！
I'd probably wanna keep that rather quiet.
不好意思，你有问题问我吗？
I'm sorry, you have some questions for me?
这位女士，你跟这个男的是什么关系？
Miss, what is your association with this man?
呃，他是我的丈夫
Er, he's my husband.
我明白了
I see.
时间并不长
Oh but only for a few days
我都不知道他在外面干些什么
I mean I don't know what he does when he's outside the house
真是谢谢你啊，亲爱的
Thank you, darling.
你看，这是我们第一次按照我的计划旅行
You see, this is the first time we're traveling my way
所以我们一定要坐飞机，这很重要
so it's very important that we make this flight
她计划的东西总是跟我的计划相反
See it's one of those her plan versus my plan, kind of things
计划？你所指的计划是什么？
What do you mean by "plan"?
你们真的应该只问我“是或不是”的问题
You really should just ask me yes or no questions.
啊，这袋子不是他的，是我的
Oh no, That's not his bag, that's my bag.
只是例行公事
It's just procedure.
我知道，但是你不明白，你看，所有东西都包得很好
Yes but you don't understand, see everything is packed perfectly.
我花了很长时间来打包好的，大约有50个折好的东西
It took me forever to do this. OK, there are like over 50 folded pieces
你真不讲理
You're mean.
好吧，你们现在可以走了
All right, you're free to go.
谢了
Thank you, thanks.
呃，关于那些紧身泳裤…我不知道它们怎么会在那里
And listen about those speedos, I don't know how they got in there
喂？
Hello
我是乔伊，我和菲比闻到有煤气从你公寓泄漏出来
Hey, it's Joey. Listen, Phoebe and I smell gas coming from your apartment.
什么？真的假的？
What? Are you serious?
乔伊闻到了煤气
Joey smells gas.
这有什么新鲜的
What else is new?
我们想进去看看，但你把我们的钥匙拿走了
And we go check it out, but you took away our keys.
那就想办法进去啊！
Well, do something!
你希望我们撞开房门？
You wanna us break down your door?
对对！
Yes!
门坏了你不会怪我们？
And you won't blame us for any damage?
不会！
No!
你确定要我们这样做吗?
OK then, you sure you wanna us do this?
不！我希望你们站在那儿，等着整个屋子都被炸飞！
No, I want you to stand there and wait for the whole place to blow up.
请再进来一下
Step back inside, please.